carcarekiosk.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy of CarCareKiosk website and Service

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**Updated: October 10, 2018**

Flatsix, LLC (“CarCareKiosk”, “we”, “our” or “us”) understands that you care how information about you is gathered, used and shared. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using carcarekiosk.com (the “Website”) and related services (the “Service”), then it will be only used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page periodically to ensure that you are happy with the changes.

Questions regarding this policy should be directed to [info@carcarekiosk.com](mailto:info@carcarekiosk.com?subject=Policy%20Question). By submitting any information to the Website, by using the Service, or by visiting the Website, you agree to be bound by these terms and the Terms of Service Agreement <https://www.carcarekiosk.com/terms>.

**WHAT WE COLLECT**

User Provided Information: You may provide us information about yourself and the vehicle(s) you drive, such as your name and email address, the year, make, model, sub-model, mileage, vehicle identification number (“VIN”) and maintenance history when you register with the Service. Any electronic correspondence with us may be retained by us. We may ask you for your other information, like your mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other personally identifiable information. You may, however, visit our Website anonymously.

Website Activity: We collect information from you when you register on the Website, search the Website, engage in a transaction, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another Website feature. We follow some of the actions you take on carcarekiosk.com, such as (but not limited to) watching a video or referring a friend.

Cookies: When you visit carcarekiosk.com, we may send one or more small non-executable text files to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets us help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the Website. A cookie does not collect personally identifiable information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can set your browser to decline them. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you can modify your browser settings to decline cookies. In addition you can delete cookies that have already been set. Typically these settings can be found in your browser settings. Another option is to check out https://www.aboutcookies.org/ for an overview on cookie settings for wide variety of web browsers.

We also use JavaScript and Log File Information that may collect and store personally identifiable information such as your IP address. These are used to facilitate more accurate reporting, improve the carcarekiosk.com experience and help us diagnose and repair problems with our Service. CarCareKiosk may use Google Analytics or Quantcast to enhance our understanding of use of the Service. Google Analytics and Quantcast collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including cookies and your IP address. Google Analytics and Quantcast also receive this information and their use of it is governed by their privacy policies. Through these means, we automatically collect information about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details that help us improve our Website to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our Website.

Third Party Log In Credentials: By logging into the Website using a set of Third Party Credentials (such as Facebook), you will be giving us access to certain general personally identifying information stored in your profiles. We do not view this information without first obtaining your consent. In some instances we will provide you tools to share our Service with other people in your networks. We encourage, and may record, the frequency of this activity.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

If you submit personal information to carcarekiosk.com, we may use that information to operate, maintain and improve the features and functionality of the Service. Personal information or content that you voluntarily submit to the Service becomes available to the public. We may use the information we collect from you, whether collected automatically or given to us voluntarily, in the following ways:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products or Service.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide the information.
  * To personalize your Website experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested and recognize you when you return to our Website.
  * To estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * To speed up your searches.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other Website feature.

We do not use your email address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent. We will use your email address to send you notices regarding the Service. If you wish to opt out of email communication from carcarekiosk.com, send an email to [info@carcarekiosk.com](mailto:info@carcarekiosk.com?subject=Opt%20Out%20of%20Email) with the words “Opt Out of Email” in the subject line. Please note that opting out may prevent you from receiving important messages regarding the Service.

If you believe that we possess your personal data and want us to delete it, please send us an email to [info@carcarekiosk.com](mailto:info@carcarekiosk.com?subject=Delete%20Personal%20Data) with the words “Delete Personal Data” in the subject line.

We use cookies, web beacons and log file information to (i) store information that allows you to log in automatically the next time you use the Service; (ii) provide customized and personalized content; (iii) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing efforts; (iv) monitor metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and (v) track your submissions.

**HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

When you create an account on our Service, some information about your account and your account activity are provided to other users of the Service. This may include the date you created your account, your member name, comments and updates you submitted, your name, or username. We do does not guarantee the truth or accuracy of any information posted by Website users on the Website.

Your carcarekiosk.com user name, not your email address, is displayed to other users of the Website when you submit content. Content submitted to our Service may be distributed through the internet and other media and may be viewed by carcarekiosk.com users or the general public.

When you complete a referral form for vehicle service, we send your information to the mechanic or car dealership highlighted in the form. By clicking the “submit” button, you are agreeing to have a mechanic or car dealer contact you for the purpose of responding to your vehicle service quote request. You understand that the dealer’s call may be using an autodialer, and that a portion of the call may be pre-recorded. Carecarekiosk.com does not provide any guarantees regarding this Service or communications or the relationship between you and the mechanic or car dealership.

**DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

CarCareKiosk may share your personally identifiable information with third parties solely for the purpose of providing Service to you. If this is done, third parties’ use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may disclose personally identifiable information: (i) if we have a good faith belief that doing so is required by a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order or otherwise required by law; (ii) to enforce our Terms of Service Agreement, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations or to protect the security or integrity of our Service; and (iii) to exercise or protect the rights or property of CarCareKiosk, our users or third parties.

We may share non-personally identifiable information such as anonymous usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, etc. with interested third parties in our sole discretion.

We may allow third-party ad servers or ad networks (such as Google AdSense or DoubleClick) to display advertisements on our Service. These third-party ad servers or ad networks may use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements that appear within the Website. When this happens, they automatically receive your IP address and other log file information. These third-party companies may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize their advertising content. We do not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent.

We also reserve the right to transfer personal information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation). Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use personal information you have provided to us in a manner that is consistent with our Privacy Policy. Following such a sale or transfer, you may contact the entity to which we transferred your personal information with any inquiries concerning the processing of that personal information.

**THIRD-PARTY SERVICES**

The Website may contain links to services and websites provided by third parties. We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Website nor the information or content contained therein. Any Personal Information provided to third-party sites or services is governed by that party’s privacy and security.

**HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION**

We use commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your Personal Information. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to our Service and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, we make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical or managerial safeguards.

However, you post information on the Website and transmit information to others through the Website at your own risk. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. Further, we urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your posts or information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your posts or information will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

**MINORS**

The privacy of young children is especially important to us. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register on our Website. If you are under 13, you are not permitted under the Terms of Service Agreement to use our Service; please do not send any information about yourself to us and stop using our Service. In the event that we learn that personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, has been collected by us, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you are between the ages of 13 and 18, please ask your parent or guardian’s permission before using the Website and our Service. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 18, please contact us at [info@carcarekiosk.com](mailto:info@carcarekiosk.com?subject=Minors).

**CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE**

If you are a California resident and use our Website or App, you are entitled to request certain information regarding our disclosure of certain “personal information” (as defined in California Civil Code Section 1798.83) to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and have provided us personal information within the last year, you may make such a request by emailing us at [info@carcarekiosk.com](mailto:info@carcarekiosk.com?subject=California%20Privacy%20Rights), and typing the following in the subject line of the e-mail: “California Privacy Rights.”

If your request is covered by the above referenced statute, within 30 days of receiving such a request, we will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties. A request may be made no more than once per calendar year and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through the e-mail address above.

**CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may update or amend this Privacy Policy at any time, with or without advance notice. In the event there are material changes in the way we treat your Personal Information, or in the Privacy Policy itself, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

Please direct any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website or any other matter to us at [info@carcarekiosk.com](mailto:info@carcarekiosk.com?subject=Privacy%20Question) or by mail at Flatsix, LLC, PO Box 70151 Milwaukee, WI 53207.
